jukeboxalive.com 2006-06-19

# JukeBoxAlive: Listen to Online Music for free and upload music

Protecting consumer privacy online is central to ByRegion.net. Accordingly, ByRegion.net pledges to keep all personal information provided by consumers and member businesses private by:

-Making sure that only designated staff have access to it.   
-Using it only for the stated purpose (the reason for which you gave it to us)

At any time, consumers and/or businesses may:

-Access and change personal information they have provided to ByRegion   
-Remove their names from ByRegion mailing lists   
-Change personal information you have given to ByRegion, to remove your name from ByRegion.net mailing lists, or for more information on how ByRegion.net uses personal information you provide, please e-mail our Customer Service Department.   

ByRegion.net does not assemble or track personal information about consumers who click on the ByRegion icon and/or visit ByRegion' website, beyond whatever information consumers voluntarily provide. ByRegion does report to member businesses the total number of people clicking on the ByRegion icon on their Web site, for example, but we do not collect or provide any identifying information about those people. We may also use such information in-house to enhance the services we offer consumers and member businesses. 

| 

As you complete your order, you'll be asked for your name, address, and credit card number. We use Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) technology to send your credit card number to our computer. SSL sends your number in an encrypted code, which only we can decode (***see footnote).

This information is sent to a credit card payment processor to validate the name, address, and credit card number \- in much the same way that restaurants and stores handle your purchases. Your encrypted credit card information is then stored in a highly protected computer. While we can keep track of your name and address from one order to the next, you will have to provide your credit card number each time you order. Your order form, including encrypted credit card number, is then archived in a highly protected computer. The credit card information cannot be accessed for future purchases.

Our transaction system currently works with Web browsers that can use SSL - such as Microsoft Internet Explorer, Netscape Navigator and the America Online browser. 

ByRegion will not provide any information about you to anyone outside the company, unless you specifically give us permission to do so.

***As reported in a recent Knight-Ridder News Service article (which appeared in the Philadelphia Inquirer), "In 1998, there were no reports of credit-card information stolen on the World Wide Web during a transfer of information over a Secure Socket Layer (SSL) line, the kind of line used by Netscape Navigator and Microsoft Explorer. There were no slip-ups. None! "
